<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
  <gameList>
        <game>
          <path>./alienplanet.gb</path>
          <name>Alien Planet</name>
          <desc>Alien Planet is a vertical shoot&apos;em-up. You control the player ship with the directional controls and use button B to shoot. Start Button pauses the game.\nThe goal of the game is to score points. If you get hit you lose your ship. You have 3 additional ships, lose them all and it&apos;s Game Over.\nSome enemies and power-stations will emit Power-containers. Catch them to raise the power of your bullets. Your bullets have 5 different levels of power. Each next level is reached after collecting 100 P-points. Your power decreases every few shots. Your power also decreases when you lose a ship.</desc>
          <image>./alienplanet.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010925T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>The New Image</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Alien Planet</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./binarychaos.gbc</path>
          <name>Binary Chaos</name>
          <desc>It is the year 2050... A new type of threat has arisen to the nation: the hacker. Yet again, another hacker, this time named J.T., has compromised national security. This time, he has everything he wants at his fingertips. All he needs to do is press one key to drop a nuke on the recently formed Mars Alliance and start a full-scale war! It is up to you to save the nation by matching up all of the blocks so you have control again. Good luck!</desc>
          <image>./binarychaos.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010227T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Stoic Software</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Binary Chaos</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./blastah.gb</path>
          <name>Blastah</name>
          <desc>Blastah is a small free GBC shoot&apos;em up game. It is mostly a quick game comedy was done in a few hours to take a part in a small game competition was organised for hobby GBC programmers.</desc>
          <image>./blastah.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010227T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Black Box</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Blastah</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./brickster.gbc</path>
          <name>Brickster</name>
          <desc> </desc>
          <image>./brickster.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>19990929T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Stephane Hockenhull</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Brickster</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./burly.gbc</path>
          <name>Burly Bear vs. The Mean Foxes</name>
          <desc>Here we have Burly Bear going around swiping at mean foxes, eating cookies, and moving from place to place once the foxes have been felled.</desc>
          <image>./burly.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120215T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Sebastian Mihai</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Burly Bear vs. The Mean Foxes</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./chuckie.gbc</path>
          <name>Chuckie Egg DX</name>
          <desc>As Hen-House Harry, the player must collect the twelve eggs positioned in each level, before a countdown timer reaches zero. In addition there are piles of seed which may be collected to increase points and stop the countdown timer for a while, but will otherwise be eaten by hens that patrol the level, causing them to pause. If the player touches a hen or falls through a gap in the bottom of the level, he loses a life. Each level is made of solid platforms, ladders and occasionally lift platforms that constantly move upwards but upon leaving the top of the screen will reappear at the bottom. Hitting the top of the screen while on one of these lifts, however, will also cause the player to lose a life.</desc>
          <image>./chuckie.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010228T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Imperfection</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Chuckie Egg DX</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game> 
        <game>
          <path>./chunkout.gbc</path>
          <name>Chunk Out</name>
          <desc>Chunkout provides a great puzzle game for young and old, with simple pick up and play gameplay that hides a depth of strategy.</desc>
          <image>./chunkout.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010508T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Chunkout Games</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Chunk Out</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./columnsdx.gbc</path>
          <name>Columns DX</name>
          <desc>Beat computer by destorying falling gems. You need to have 3 or more in column or row to destory them.</desc>
          <image>./columnsdx.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20000509T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Unknown</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Columns DX</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./drunkenpooper.gb</path>
          <name>Drunken Pooper</name>
          <desc>After one drunk night I woke up to find a surprise on the shower floor. My roomate was of course passed out in his bed. I knew I didn&apos;t do it, so it had to be him. When he finally woke up, he had no memory of the incident. Only after realizing in his drunken state that he forgot to wipe, did he come clean. So as penance I started making this game to piss him off. And cause it was easy enough for me to program. It actually turned into a half way fun game. And there&apos;s a funny secret. Have fun.</desc>
          <image>./drunkenpooper.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010216T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Matt Ripston</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Drunken Pooper</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./finalblade.gbc</path>
          <name>Final Blade</name>
          <desc>Throughout the game, you will encounter blocks that will obstruct your path. In order to pass these blocks, you must first find the switch to change the block and press it. During the game, you have two types of weapons available to you: Sword, Sword Combos &amp; Fireball.</desc>
          <image>./finalblade.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010228T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Red Baaron Blue Samurai</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Final Blade</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>      
        <game>
          <path>./fxshooter.gbc</path>
          <name>FX Shooter G: MiniRPG2 Story</name>
          <desc>It is a conversion of QBasic version of FX Shooter2: MiniRPG2 story. Storyline is almost same as MiniRPG2 (which is also a very old simple RPG game for QBasic, also made by me,Change-V). 4 stages with horizontal scrolling background (originally 6 stages, but I didn&apos;t have time to add all). I will add 2 stages later. Each stages has end boss. You can shoot 2 bullets at a time. 3 steps of power up (for each power ups, you will shoot little bit bigger bullet). HP and power will reset when you advance to next stage. HP system, so one hit will not kill you.</desc>
          <image>./fxshooter.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010228T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Change-V, Jaws-V</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>FX Shooter G: MiniRPG2 Story</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./frikirace.gb</path>
          <name>Friki Race</name>
          <desc>Friki Race is a pretty simple car racing game, in which you must reach the goal in time through 3 different stages. Also you have to overtake as many rivals as possible to become the first in the ranking.</desc>
          <image>./frikirace.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>19990926T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Enrique Sanchez Rosa</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Friki Race</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./gbamatron.gb</path>
          <name>GBamaTron</name>
          <desc>You are Doctor Burkanovich, whose laboratory biorobots have mutated, gone crazy and they kill now. But not everything is lost. Thanks to the rechargable blaster, there is a chance for escape. Use it for annihilating the robots and keep away from the electrical walls. And watch out for Sonia and Doti. Good Luck!\nDuring the game use the D-Pad for moving, A-Button to lock your firing direction, B-Button to forbid firing in left and right and Start for pause. The shooting is automatic.</desc>
          <image>./gbamatron.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20060402T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Ventzislav Tzvetkov</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>GBamaTron</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./geometrix.gbc</path>
          <name>Geometrix</name>
          <desc>This is a very simple puzzle game in which the objective is to create rows or columns of 3 or more of the same geometric form. Each row or column of 3 is worth 1 point, a line of 4 elements is considered to be 2 lines of 3 together, so it&apos;s worth 2 points, etc. If removing a line allows another one to be removed, the combo counter increases and the score of that removal is multiplied by it. The combo counter may increase up to 9. As soon as new geometric forms come into the screen from the top, or the chain stops, the combo counter will go back to 1.</desc>
          <image>./geometrix.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20150312T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>AntonioND/SkyLyrac (Antonio Nino Diaz)</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Geometrix</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./horribledemon3.gb</path>
          <name>Horrible Demon III, The</name>
          <desc>RPG adventure game.  Rescue your sister (and the world) from the Horrible Demon, and become king in the process!</desc>
          <image>./horribledemon3.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010325T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Bertil Horberg</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Horrible Demon III, The</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./ironhike.gbc</path>
          <name>Iron Hike</name>
          <desc>Jump n Run side-scroller game like Mario.</desc>
          <image>./ironhike.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20000115T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Mikael Andersson</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Iron Hike</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>      
        <game>
          <path>./ishallbequeen.gb</path>
          <name>I Shall Be Queen</name>
          <desc>A double dragon-style beat-em-up. There are a couple of bugs with the game and it gets bloody tough to beat. Also I had to cut out the boss fight due to ROM and time limitations. There&apos;s a few easter eggs dotted around, have fun!</desc>
          <image>./ishallbequeen.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20060814T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Refresh Games</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>I Shall Be Queen</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./jetpakdx.gb</path>
          <name>Jet Pak DX</name>
          <desc>Lost, stranded on a strange planet. Light years away from home. You scramble your way home, planet hopping. Burning the fuel you collect in the spaceships you build, just to get that bit closer to home.</desc>
          <image>./jetpakdx.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>19990705T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Quang Vinh Nguyen</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Jet Pak DX</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>       
        <game>
          <path>./jumpik.gbc</path>
          <name>Jumpik</name>
          <desc>Avoid the toxic pools and collect the coins in this platformer game inspired by all the old classics.</desc>
          <image>./jumpik.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010113T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Small Blue Cube</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Jumpik</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game> 
        <game>
          <path>./jumpman86.gbc</path>
          <name>Jumpman 86</name>
          <desc>Jumpman 86 is a platform game that features thirty unique levels where the player must defuse all of the bombs on screen by running into them.</desc>
          <image>./jumpman86.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010325T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Par Johannesson</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Jumpman 86</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./klondike.gbc</path>
          <name>Klondike</name>
          <desc>Card game.\nD-pad: controls mouse pointer; A: Action button, select a card (dot shows which card is active) then move pointer to another card and press &apos;A&apos; again to place the active card if the move is legal; B: Moves the card under the pointer to the goal piles if the move is legal; START: Pauses the game, and allows the player to change the game style (whether to draw 1 or 3 cards) SELECT+DOWN: Redeals the cards.</desc>
          <image>./klondike.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010325T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Harold Toler</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Klondike</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game>
          <path>./manicminer.gbc</path>
          <name>Manic Miner</name>
          <desc>In each of the twenty caverns, each one screen in size, are several flashing objects, which the player must collect before Willy&apos;s oxygen supply runs out. Once the player has collected the objects in one cavern, they must then go to the now-flashing portal, which will take them to the next cavern. The player must avoid enemies, which move along predefined paths at constant speeds. Willy can also be killed by falling too far, so players must time the precision of jumps and other movements to prevent such falls or collisions with the enemies.</desc>
          <image>./manicminer.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>19990827T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Paul Taylor</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Manic Miner</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game>
          <path>./meanmrmustard.gb</path>
          <name>Mean Mr. Mustard</name>
          <desc>The game that combines the telephone game with simple drawing.</desc>
          <image>./meanmrmustard.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20000501T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Henik Jansson, Mikael Backlund</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Mean Mr. Mustard</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game>
          <path>./perplexdx.gbc</path>
          <name>Perplex DX</name>
          <desc>You have to connect the red stones with the grey stones to colourize them also to red. If you get all the stones red in the level, then you will enter the next one. You have to pass 64 levels. Every level is tested and has 100% a solution.  Don&apos;t be boried, if you don&apos;t manage a level. You have a password function, to try it later again...</desc>
          <image>./perplexdx.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010227T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Smacks-Designs</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Perplex DX</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game>
          <path>./presentpanic.gbc</path>
          <name>Present Panic</name>
          <desc>It&apos;s Christmas Eve and Santa&apos;s Grotto, deep in the North Pole, is getting ready for the big day. Unknown to Santa though, his elves are planning a mass strike, and have spread all the presents for all the children of the world throughout the North Pole complex. As Santa Claus, you must find all the presents and save Christmas! The game is split up into eight levels. In each level, you must collect all the presents, and make your way to the exit, which wll take you on to the next level. You start with ten lives, and you can find more along the way. Each level also has a time limit.</desc>
          <image>./presentpanic.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010710T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>SuperNova Software</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Present Panic</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game>
          <path>./skoardy.gb</path>
          <name>Skoardy</name>
          <desc>Guide the red dot around the maze to the exit. You can&apos;t stop, only turn. Too slow and you crash which loses a life. You have 3 lives to finish all 10 levels. Oh yes, collect the pots too.</desc>
          <image>./skoardy.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>19990921T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Darren Hebden</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Skoardy</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game>
          <path>./stalker.gbc</path>
          <name>Stalker</name>
          <desc>Kill all enemy squads and mechanized walkers. Pick up items for extra weapons and energy.</desc>
          <image>./stalker.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010228T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>True Video</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Stalker</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./superninja.gbc</path>
          <name>Super Ninja</name>
          <desc>Possibly one of the only games with Ninja in the title that doesn&apos;t actually feature any Ninjas - yet...</desc>
          <image>./superninja.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010228T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>TornPocket</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Super Ninja</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./theycamefromouterspace.gb</path>
          <name>They came from outer space...</name>
          <desc>The game is a clone of the classic game of &apos;Space Invaders&apos;. The goal is simple: just destory as many of the alien invaders to gain high scores. There are some bonuses to collect by shooting down alien UFO&apos;s giving you more firepower to kill the invaders more easily.</desc>
          <image>./theycamefromouterspace.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010228T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Carcatau Development</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>They came from outer space...</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>   
       <game>
          <path>./tochi.gbc</path>
          <name>Tochi</name>
          <desc>Tochi is a puzzle game in the vein of Sonic Team&apos;s Chu Chu Rocket. Different colored Tochis must be directed to their appropriate home by placing arrows in their path.</desc>
          <image>./tochi.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20000829T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Ben Hopkins</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Tochi</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>       
       <game>
          <path>./tomatom.gbc</path>
          <name>Tom Atom</name>
          <desc>An amazing RPG game for GBC!</desc>
          <image>./tomatom.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20021213T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Small Blue Cube</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Tom Atom</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>   
       <game>
          <path>./ultima3.gb</path>
          <name>Ultima III</name>
          <desc>Ultima 3 for Gameboy Color.\nPress the A button to bring up the menu and to make selections\nPress the B button to pass or to cancel out of menus\nPress the D-Pad to move around</desc>
          <image>./ultima3.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010419T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Sven Carlberg</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Ultima III</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>       
  </gameList>