<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
  <gameList>
        <game>
          <path>./blastah.gb</path>
          <name>Blastah</name>
          <desc>Blastah is a small free GBC shoot&apos;em up game. It is mostly a quick game comedy was done in a few hours to take a part in a small game competition was organised for hobby GBC programmers.</desc>
          <image>./blastah.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010227T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Black Box</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Blastah</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./brickster.gbc</path>
          <name>Brickster</name>
          <desc>Arkanoid type of game for gameboy color.</desc>
          <image>./brickster.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>19990929T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Stephane Hockenhull</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Brickster</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./burly.gbc</path>
          <name>Burly Bear vs. The Mean Foxes</name>
          <desc>Here we have Burly Bear going around swiping at mean foxes, eating cookies, and moving from place to place once the foxes have been felled.</desc>
          <image>./burly.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120215T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Sebastian Mihai</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Burly Bear vs. The Mean Foxes</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./geometrix.gbc</path>
          <name>Geometrix</name>
          <desc>This is a very simple puzzle game in which the objective is to create rows or columns of 3 or more of the same geometric form. Each row or column of 3 is worth 1 point, a line of 4 elements is considered to be 2 lines of 3 together, so it&apos;s worth 2 points, etc. If removing a line allows another one to be removed, the combo counter increases and the score of that removal is multiplied by it. The combo counter may increase up to 9. As soon as new geometric forms come into the screen from the top, or the chain stops, the combo counter will go back to 1.</desc>
          <image>./geometrix.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20150312T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>AntonioND/SkyLyrac (Antonio Nino Diaz)</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Geometrix</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./klondike.gbc</path>
          <name>Klondike</name>
          <desc>Card game.. D-pad: controls mouse pointer; A: Action button, select a card (dot shows which card is active) then move pointer to another card and press &apos;A&apos; again to place the active card if the move is legal; B: Moves the card under the pointer to the goal piles if the move is legal; START: Pauses the game, and allows the player to change the game style (whether to draw 1 or 3 cards) SELECT+DOWN: Redeals the cards.</desc>
          <image>./klondike.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20010325T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Harold Toler</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>Klondike</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./ucity.gbc</path>
          <name>uCity</name>
          <desc>This is uCity (pronounced &apos;micro-city&apos;), the open-source city-building game for Game Boy Color.</desc>
          <image>./ucity.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20180131T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>AntonioND/SkyLyrac (Antonio Nino Diaz)</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>uCity</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>      
  </gameList>